Narrator: Clothes
Speaker: blouse
Narrator: 14
Speaker: cardigan
Narrator: 3
Speaker: coat
Narrator: 2
Speaker: dress
Narrator: 12
Speaker: hoodie
Narrator: 9
Speaker: jacket
Narrator: 5
Speaker: jeans
Narrator: 15
Speaker: leggings
Narrator: 19
Speaker: pyjamas
Narrator: 8
Speaker: shirt
Narrator: 1
Speaker: shorts
Narrator: 6
Speaker: skirt
Narrator: 21
Speaker: socks
Narrator: 7
Speaker: suit
Narrator: 17
Speaker: sweater
Narrator: 20
Speaker: tights
Narrator: 4
Speaker: top
Narrator: 10
Speaker: tracksuit
Narrator: 13
Speaker: trousers
Narrator: 16
Speaker: T-shirt
Narrator: 18
Speaker: underwear
Narrator: Footwear
Speaker: boots
Narrator: 26
Speaker: flip-flops
Narrator: 23
Speaker: sandals
Narrator: 24
Speaker: shoes
Narrator: 22
Speaker: trainers
Narrator: Accessories
Speaker: belt
Narrator: 31
Speaker: cap
Narrator: 29
Speaker: gloves
Narrator: 32
Speaker: hat
Narrator: 30
Speaker: scarf
Narrator: 28
Speaker: tie
Narrator: Jewellery
Speaker: bracelet
Narrator: 33
Speaker: earrings
Narrator: 36
Speaker: necklace
Narrator: 35
Speaker: ring